Topical files 2
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Topical files 2
2.1.9.5
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1616
- Topical files 2, 2.1.9.5
  - Chaquib Abdul-Karim, 1952; 33 (Box 1616)
    - [Chaquib Abdul-Karim], 1
  - Margaret Anastasio, 1975; 34 (Box 1616)
    - [Margaret Anastasio: Lowell Thomas sitting] [1940], 1
    - Verso: 1940, 1-verso
    - [Margaret Anastasio: Lowell Thomas sitting]Kodak building, 2
    - Verso: Kodak building, 2-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Mrs. E. R. Margaret Anastasio], 3
  - John Anderson [color photograph], 1968; 35 (Box 1616)
    - [John Anderson:] Solo facta jucy [Joey] y los papa's [?], 1
    - Verso: Solo facta jucy [Joey] y los papa's [?], 1-verso
  - W. F. Andrews ("Andy"&) [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas] [color photograph], 1957; 36 (Box 1616)
    - Caption: Pt. Barrow, Alaska. 1957 with Lowell Thomas; Verso: W.F. Andrews ("Andy") with Lowell Thomas at Pt. Barrow, Alaska, 1957, 1
    - Verso: W.F. Andrews ("Andy") with Lowell Thomas at Pt. Barrow, Alaska, 1957, 1-verso
  - M. Ray Applegate [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1952; 37 (Box 1616)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Applegate Advertising Agency concerning permission to use photograph], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [response from Lowell Thomas from Applegate Advertising Agency concerning permission to use photograph], 2
    - [photograph possibly used by Applegate Advertising Agency], 3
  - Richard D. Applegate [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], circa 1940s; 38 (Box 1616)
    - [Richard D. Applegate: Four men in uniform standing next to plane. Lowell Thomas at right], 1
  - N. W. Ayer and Son [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], circa 1946; 39 (Box 1616)
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 3, document describing N.W. Ayer Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 3, document describing N.W. Ayer Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of 3, document describing N.W. Ayer Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 2, second document describing N.W. Ayer Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 2, second document describing N.W. Ayer Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography], 5
    - Judges of the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography held in Philadelphia, April 17, under the auspices of N.W. Ayer & Son, Inc. Left to right: Harold Van Doren, industrial designer, Laurence B. Siegfried, type expert, and Lowell Thomas, radio commentator., 6
    - Note[PDF]: Judges of the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography held in Philadelphia, April 17, under the auspices of N.W. Ayer & Son, Inc. Left to right: Harold Van Doren, industrial designer, Laurence B. Siegfried, type expert, and Lowell Thomas, radio commentator., 7
    - Page one of the Rochester Post-Bulletin, Rochesterm Minn. For March 13, winner of the F. Wayland Ayer Cup, also shown, in the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography, held in Philadelphia April 17, under the auspices of N.W. Ayer & son Inc., 8
    - Note[PDF]: Page one of the Rochester Post-Bulletin, Rochesterm Minn. For March 13, winner of the F. Wayland Ayer Cup, also shown, in the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography, held in Philadelphia April 17, under the auspices of N.W. Ayer & son Inc., 9
    - Winners of Honorable Mentions among paper of more than 50,000 circul;ation in te 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography held in Philadelphia April 17, under the auspicies of N. W. Ayer & Son, Inc. Left to right: First Honorable Mention; Courier-Journal, Louisville, KY.; Second Honorable Mention; Richmond Times-Dispatch, Richmond, VA.; Third Honorable Mention, The Christian Science Monitor, Boston, Mass., 10
    - Note[PDF]: Winners of Honorable Mentions among paper of more than 50,000 circul;ation in te 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography held in Philadelphia April 17, under the auspicies of N. W. Ayer & Son, Inc. Left to right: First Honorable Mention; Courier-Journal, Louisville, KY.; Second Honorable Mention; Richmond Times-Dispatch, Richmond, VA.; Third Honorable Mention, The Christian Science Monitor, Boston, Mass., 11
    - Winners of Honorable Mention amaong [among] papers of 10,000 to 50,000 circulation in the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography held in Philadelphia April 17, under the auspicies of N. W. Ayer & Son, Inc. Left to right: First Honorable Mention, Durham Morning Herald, Durham, N.C.; Second Honorable Mention, Reading Eagle, Reading, PA.; Third Honorable Mention, Rutland Herald, Rutland, VT., 12
    - Note[PDF]: Winners of Honorable Mention amaong [among]]papers of 10,000 to 50,000 circulation in the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography held in Philadelphia April 17, under the auspicies of N. W. Ayer & Son, Inc. Left to right: First Honorable Mention, Durham Morning Herald, Durham, N.C.; Second Honorable Mention, Reading Eagle, Reading, PA.; Third Honorable Mention, Rutland Herald, Rutland, VT., 13
    - Winners of Honorable Mention amaong [among] papers of less than 10,000 circulation in the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography held in Philadelphia April 17, under the auspicies of N. W. Ayer & Son, Inc. Left to right, First Honorable Mention: Owensboro Inquirer, Owensboro, KY.; Socond Honorable Mention: The Antigo Daily Journal, Antigo, Wisc.; Third Honorable Mention: Sante Fe New Mexican, Santa Fe, New Mexico., 14
    - Note[PDF]: Winners of Honorable Mention among papers of less than 10,000 circulation in the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typography held in Philadelphia April 17, under the auspicies of N. W. Ayer & Son, Inc. Left to right, First Honorable Mention: Owensboro Inquirer, Owensboro, KY.; Socond Honorable Mention: The Antigo Daily Journal, Antigo, Wisc.; Third Honorable Mention: Sante Fe New Mexican, Santa Fe, New Mexico., 15
    - The Gazette & Daily, York, PA. winner of the Certificate for Tabloids, regardless of circularion, in the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typorgraphy held in Philadelphia, April 17, under the auspicies of N.W. Ayer & Son, Inc., 16
    - Note[PDF]: The Gazette & Daily, York, PA. winner of the Certificate for Tabloids, regardless of circularion, in the 16th Annual Exhibition of Newspaper Typorgraphy held in Philadelphia, April 17, under the auspicies of N.W. Ayer & Son, Inc., 17
  - Retta Barnette, undated; 40 (Box 1616)
    - Retta Barnette [holding a parrot], 1
    - Verso: Retta Barnette, 1-verso
  - Frank J. Berger, 1955; 41 (Box 1616)
    - Caption: Best Regards, Frank + Natalie, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter from Frank Berger to Mr. and Mrs. T[homas], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter from Frank Berger to Mr. and Mrs. T[homas], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of letter from Frank Berger to Mr. and Mrs. T[homas], 4
  - Herbert D. Bergman, 1976; 42 (Box 1616)
    - Dr. Lowell Thomas, With my respect, admiration and best wishes always. Respectfully your's [signed] Herbert J. Bergman TSgt. (USAF-Ret.) 1976, 1
    - Verso: Dr. Lowell Thomas, With my respect, admiration and best wishes always. Respectfully your's [signed] Herbert J. Bergman TSgt. (USAF-Ret.) 1976, 1-verso
  - William B. Black [color photographs], 1976; 43 (Box 1616)
    - One of four naval carriage guns for Valkyrie. 1" Bore [signed] W. Black [?], 1
    - Verso: One of four naval carriage guns for Valkyrie. 1" Bore [signed] W. Black [?], 1-verso
    - "The Valkyrie Brigantine" 23 tons displacement, 45' on deck, 56' over-all, 51' Ht. of Main, 13'7" Beam, 6'2" Draft [illegible], 2
    - Verso: "The Valkyrie Brigantine" 23 tons displacement, 45' on deck, 56' over-all, 51' Ht. of Main, 13'7" Beam, 6'2" Draft [illegible], 2-verso
    - "The Valkyrie Brigantine" on Stanboul yack [starboard tack?], 3
    - Verso: "The Valkyrie Brigantine" on Stanboul yack [starboard tack?], 3-verso
    - Rear Admiral Ed Fleck and I and our wives had Colonial costumes made for the Bicentennial. Mine is of a Continental Navy Commodore of 1777. One doesn't have to be crazy, - but it helps! - Dick, 4
    - Verso: Rear Admiral Ed Fleck and I and our wives had Colonial costumes made for the Bicentennial. Mine is of a Continental Navy Commodore of 1777. One doesn't have to be crazy, - but it helps! - Dick, 4-verso
  - Marie Blood [color photograph], 1979; 44 (Box 1616)
    - Me (on right) and a friend at Gold Rush Days, Valdez, Alaska August, 1979, 1
    - Verso: Me (on right) and a friend at Gold Rush Days, Valdez, Alaska August, 1979, 1-verso
  - Nora and Heriberto Bohtlingk, circa 1957; 45 (Box 1616)
    - [inside of card] With all good wishes for Christmas and the New Year from Nora and Heriberto Bohtlingk. After our trip to India and around the world we enjoyed your 'Land of the Black Pagoda' which you sent us after the dinner party at the Palmeds last January - Konarek[?] was certanly amazing, 1
    - Verso: [inside of card] With all good wishes for Christmas and the New Year from Nora and Heriberto Bohtlingk. After our trip to India and around the world we enjoyed your 'Land of the Black Pagoda' which you sent us after the dinner party at the Palmeds last January - Konarek[?] was certanly amazing, 1-verso
  - Hazel and Howell Bond, circa 1957; 46 (Box 1616)
    - Caption: Seasons Greetings and Aloha from Hazel and Howell (Bond); Verso: 2146 Damon St., Honolulu 14, Hawaii, 1
    - Verso: 2146 Damon St., Honolulu 14, Hawaii, 1-verso
  - Colonel and Mrs. Daniel F. Boone [color photograph], 1979; 47 (Box 1616)
    - Col. & Mrs. Daniel F. Boone, 420 Dunes Drive, Dunes Section, Myrtle Beach, SC 29577 - May 21, '77, 1
    - Verso: Col. & Mrs. Daniel F. Boone, 420 Dunes Drive, Dunes Section, Myrtle Beach, SC 29577 - May 21, '77, 1-verso
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Dan Boone], 2
  Box 1617
- Topical files 2, 2.1.9.5
  - Houston Branch, 1956; 1 (Box 1617)
    - [Houston branch: submarine] exterior view[?] new window, 1
    - Verso: exterior view[?] new window, 1-verso
    - [Houston branch: submarine]Interior view - New Camera window, 2
    - Verso: Interior view - New Camera window, 2-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Houston Branch], 3
  - Clarita and Alec Bright [color photograph], circa 1965; 2 (Box 1617)
    - Caption: Merry Christmas, Happy New Year; You gave us the best outing he wave ever had in New York. Your tradition - solid gentle fun-warmed and carried the party. We hope to see you on the slopes. Clarite and Abe Bight and Snorri - Sierra - Cameron, 1
  - Marjan Frank Broda, 1944; 3 (Box 1617)
    - Marjan Frank Broda, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Marjau Frank Broda], 2
  - C. O. Brown, 1953; 4 (Box 1617)
    - [C.O. Brown: a sleigh], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 2, letter to Lowell Thomas from C. O. Brown], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 2, letter to Lowell Thomas from C. O. Brown], 3
  - Larry Dean Brown [color photograph], 1976; 5 (Box 1617)
    - Taken Graduation Day, June 11, '76 at Columbus, Ohio O.S.U. Dr. Larry Dean Brown Grandson of Lucille and J.R. Jackson, 1
    - Verso: Taken Graduation Day, June 11, '76 at Columbus, Ohio O.S.U. Dr. Larry Dean Brown Grandson of Lucille and J.R. Jackson, 1-verso
  - Marshall A. Brown, 1944; 6 (Box 1617)
    - [horse drawn sleigh], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Marshall A. Brown], 2
  - Olga M. Buck, 1962; 7 (Box 1617)
    - [Olga M. Buck:]This is a striper I caught under one of Jones Beach Causeway bridges 1958 in May, 1
    - Verso: This is a striper I caught under one of Jones Beach Causeway bridges 1958 in May, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 2, letter to Lowell Thomas from Olga M. Buck], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 2, letter to Lowell Thomas from Olga M. Buck], 3
  - Buick Motor Division [includes photographs of Lowell Thomas], 1942; 8 (Box 1617)
    - Note[PDF]: [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Frank Webb, Public Relations for Buick Motor Division], 1
    - [Buick Motor Division:][Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. with J. H. Larkin and C. E. Woollever and others], 2
    - [Buick Motor Division:][Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. with J. H. Larkin and C. E. Woollever and others], 3
    - [Buick Motor Division:][Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. with J. H. Larkin and C. E. Woollever and others], 4
  - Stanley F. Carey, 1977; 9 (Box 1617)
    - [Stanley F. Carey:] A Copy of "the other side" of [?] - Playing for many [?] all over the world - But no pay-, 1
    - Verso: A Copy of "the other side" of [?] - Playing for many [?] all over the world - But no pay-, 1-verso
  - Robert L. Carpenter, 1949; 10 (Box 1617)
    - [Robert L. Carpenter:]The former carpenter home, [?] + Bradly St - Harris Park, NJ, 1
    - Verso: The former carpenter home, [?] + Bradly St - Harris Park, NJ, 1-verso
  - James T. Chamness [color photograph], 1980; 11 (Box 1617)
    - [James T. Chamness: Twin babies], 1
  - Fred G. Clark [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1958; 12 (Box 1617)
    - [Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [Herbert Hoover, front row center], 2
    - [Fred G. Clark: People putting on a play], 3
    - [Fred G. Clark: Close-up of a man], 4
    - [Fred G. Clark: Two men laughing], 5
    - Note: [envelope from Fred G. Clark], 6
  - Arthur J. Conlon [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], circa 1930s; 13 (Box 1617)
    - [Arthur J. Conlon:][Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Nancy Cooke [color photograph], 1979; 14 (Box 1617)
    - [Nancy Cooke [color photo]: Bride and groom], 1
  - Ronald Crane [color photograph], 1979; 15 (Box 1617)
    - [Ronald Crane: Boy standing in front of little airplane], 1
  - Betty Cross [color photograph], 1980; 16 (Box 1617)
    - Rip Rankin + Betty Cross (Mrs. James), Cripple Creek - Lucy Welty's white house on top of hill, 1
    - Verso: Rip Rankin + Betty Cross (Mrs. James), Cripple Creek - Lucy Welty's white house on top of hill, 1-verso
  - Tom Curry [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1946; 17 (Box 1617)
    - [Tom Curry: Lowell Thomas and another man (Tom Curry?) in uniform] Rome 5-45, 1
    - Verso: Rome 5-45, 1-verso
    - [Woman standing], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Tom Curry], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Tom Curry], 4
    - Note: Call it off; on? [Tom Curry], 5
  - Nola and Glenn Dolberg, 1975; 18 (Box 1617)
    - [Nola and Glenn Dolberg:]Nola Luxford [illegible] Jan. 1975, 1
    - Verso: Nola Luxford [illegible] Jan. 1975, 1-verso
  - Mina Dole, 1973; 19 (Box 1617)
    - Bill, now 17yrs. (The Clark) 6'1; Scott 15 yrs 6'; Julie 14 years 5'3" still as sweet (won her first Home Ribbon at camp!); Mina The Doles in St. Louis 3/60, 1
    - Verso: Bill, now 17yrs. (The Clark) 6'1; Scott 15 yrs 6'; Julie 14 years 5'3" still as sweet (won her first Home Ribbon at camp!); Mina The Doles in St. Louis 3/60, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 2, letter to Lowell Thomas from Mina Dole], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 2, letter to Lowell Thomas from Mina Dole], 3
  - Dixie Dowrie, undated; 20 (Box 1617)
    - [Dixie Dowrie:]Stowe Vt. 1940? Or 41?, 1
    - Verso: Stowe Vt. 1940? Or 41?, 1-verso
    - [Dixie Dowrie:]Bousquet's[?]- 1943, 2
    - Verso: Bousquet's[?]- 1943, 2-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Dixie Dowrie], 3
  - Peter Dumont, 1944; 21 (Box 1617)
    - Residence of Peter Dumont, White Stucco house Green roof and blinds. Mt. Horel Rd. Between Inberly Cornr and Martinsville, KS Motor-Route Civil No 545, 1
    - Verso: Residence of Peter Dumont, White Stucco house Green roof and blinds. Mt. Horel Rd. Between Inberly Cornr and Martinsville, KS Motor-Route Civil No 545, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Peter Drummond], 2
    - Note: [envelope], 3
  - Boontown Elks, 1941; 22 (Box 1617)
    - [Boontown Elks] Feb 3 1941, 1
    - Verso: Feb 3 1941, 1-verso
    - Note: "Gertrude", a victum of infantile paralysis, was found by the Boonton Elks' Crippled Children Committee when eleven years of age. She could not walk or even stand on her feet. After three years' treatment she was returned home with only a slight limp and found employment. She was married three years ago ans is shown above with her two-year-old son. Is crippled children work worth while? February 3, 1941., 2
  - John Elliott [includes photographs of Lowell Thomas] [color photographs], 1973; 23 (Box 1617)
    - [John Elliot: Man standing with Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [John Elliot: Man standing with Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [John Elliot: Two men standing with Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [John Elliot: Two men standing with Lowell Thomas], 4
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Brick E.], 5
  - Violet and Frank Fisher, 1941; 24 (Box 1617)
    - Caption: In Tibet from "Journey into China." Violet Cressy-Marcks, 1
    - Verso: [inside of card] Greetings and Good Luck in a hard but Glorious 1941 from Violet & Frank Fisher, 1-verso
  - G - miscellaneous, 1943 - circa 1950; 25 (Box 1617)
    - [G- miscellaneous:]Peruvian Lodge Alta, 1
    - Verso: Peruvian Lodge Alta; taken from Mayor Watson's cabin, 1-verso
    - [G-miscellaneous:]The picture gallery in my Air Room. People worked for or with them the years&, 2
    - Verso: The picture gallery in my Air Room. People worked for or with them the years&, 2-verso
    - [G-miscellaneous:]Norfolk Naval Band, Portsmouth, VA., 3
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Gene], 4
  - Ewing Galloway, 1952; 26 (Box 1617)
    - [Erwing Galloway: Man standing on top of cylinders], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Ewing Galloway], 2
  - Joe Girard, circa 1975; 27 (Box 1617)
    - Caption: Lowell Thomas: "You are an idol" Best of Luck Always [signed] Joe Girard; 38th President of The United States of America Gerald R. Ford, Rear Admiral United States Nevy Lee E. Landes Joe Girard World's No. 1 Automobile and Truck Retail Salesman 10 Consecutive Years, 1
    - Caption: Joe Girard World's No. 1 Automobile and Truck Retail Salesman 10 Consecutive Years, 2
    - Note[PDF]: Joe Girard, What Makes Him No. 1 Car & Truck Salesman in the World?, 3
    - Note[PDF]: Joe Girard's Sales Training Library, 4
    - Note[PDF]: Now& You can have the world's greatest salesman on your staff, permanently! Here's how&, 5
    - Note[PDF]: Joe Girard's Sales Training Library, This seven-volume film library consists of &, 6
  - Clayton Spaulding Going, 1943; 28 (Box 1617)
    - Clayton Spaulding Going "Bumpy" 7 mos., 1
    - Verso: Clayton Spaulding Going "Bumpy" 7 mos., 1-verso
    - [Clayton Spaulding:]The 1963 National Amateur golf champ! Note wrist cock and left hand action! A Natural! 7 mos., 2
    - Verso: The 1963 National Amateur golf champ! Note wrist cock and left hand action! A Natural! 7 mos., 2-verso
    - [Clayton Spaulding:]Listening to his favorite news commentator before hitting the hay! He intends to be a well informed big guy someday! 7 mos., 3
    - Verso: Listening to his favorite news commentator before hitting the hay! He intends to be a well informed big guy someday! 7 mos., 3-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Clayton Spalding, USA Office of War Information]: Introducing your newest and youngest listener!, 4
  - Edward Stanley Gomme, 1977; 29 (Box 1617)
    - [Edward Stanley Gomme:]Name of plane was Lorraine #(249) Picture was taken on Okinawa Island on Aug 6, 1945. It came back from a mission to Hiroshima Japan&, 1
    - Verso[PDF]: Name of plane was Lorraine #(249) Picture was taken on Okinawa Island on Aug 6, 1945. It came back from a mission to Hiroshima Japan&, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Edward Stanley Gomme], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Edward Stanley Gomme], 3
  - Al Gordon [color photograph], 1972; 30 (Box 1617)
    - Taken on Oct 30 - 1971. I was M.C. at a Holloween party Al Gordon, 1
    - Verso: Taken on Oct 30 - 1971. I was M.C. at a Holloween party Al Gordon, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Al Gordon], 2
  - Albro B. Gregory [color photograph], 1980; 31 (Box 1617)
    - [Albro B. Gregory: Man and woman holding drinks], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Albro B. Gregory], 2
  - Susan Grogan, 1958; 32 (Box 1617)
    - Susan Grogan, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Susan Grogan], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Susan Grogan], 3
  - Merle H. Guise, 1962; 33 (Box 1617)
    - [Merle H. Guise:]Arctic village, Alaska Aug. 1962. Shaking hands with last Survivor Gilbert, 80, blind of my famous expedition of 1925 take medicines "Flu" epidem.; Merle H. Guise Box 2705 Palm Springs, Calif, 1
    - Verso: Arctic village, Alaska Aug. 1962. Shaking hands with last Survivor Gilbert, 80, blind of my famous expedition of 1925 take medicines "Flu" epidem.; Merle H. Guise Box 2705 Palm Springs, Calif, 1-verso
    - [Merle H. Guise:]Arctic village, Alaska Aug 1962. Back to the old "Cache." Famous expedition of 1925 take medicines in "Flu" Epidemic of 1925, 2
    - Verso: Arctic village, Alaska Aug 1962. Back to the old "Cache." Famous expedition of 1925 take medicines in "Flu" Epidemic of 1925, 2-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Merle H. Guise concerning Seppala piece], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Merle H. Guise concerning Seppala piece], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas concerning Merle H. Guise], 5
  - H - Miscellaneous [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1944 - 1945; 34 (Box 1617)
    - [H-miscellaneous:]Boca Raton 1945 [Four people seated. Lowell Thomas second from left], 1
    - Verso: Boca Raton 1945, 1-verso
    - [H-miscellaneous:]Note: [note to Lowell Thomas concerning Florida], 2
  - Maude Hadden, 1946; 35 (Box 1617)
    - [Maude Hadden: Large group picture outside by trees], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Maude Hadden], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Maude Hadden], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Maude Hadden], 4
  - Charles G. Hagedorn [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1972 - 1974; 36 (Box 1617)
    - Dear Lowell: I thought you ment wat this as a momento of a stimulating luncheon!; Cordially, [signed] Charles G. Hagedorn, 1
    - Note: Dear Lowell: I thought you might want this as a momento of a stimulating luncheon!; Cordially, [signed] Charles G. Hagedorn, 2
  - Johnny Haines, 1970; 37 (Box 1617)
    - Johnny Haines; Oct 1970, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Johnny Haines], 2
  - E. E. Hale, 1943; 38 (Box 1617)
    - [E.E. Hale:]Greer-Hale Chinchilla Ranch, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from E. E. Hale], 2
  - Mary Otwell Hall [color photograph], 1967 - 1974; 39 (Box 1617)
    - [Marty Otwell:]Caption: The Halls, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of 4 of letter 1 to Lowell Thomas from Mary Otwell Hall], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of 4 of letter 1 to Lowell Thomas from Mary Otwell Hall], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of 4 of letter 1 to Lowell Thomas from Mary Otwell Hall], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4 of 4 of letter 1 to Lowell Thomas from Mary Otwell Hall], 5
    - [Two men and a woman standing together], 6
    - Note[PDF]: [Letter 2 to Lowell Thomas from Mary Otwell Hall], 7
  - Andy Will Hatch, 1947; 40 (Box 1617)
    - [Andy Will Hatch:]Log Cabin, Maine "Deep in the Maine woods", 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Andy Will Hatch], 2
  - Harmon R. Helmericks [color photograph], 1974; 41 (Box 1617)
    - [Harmon R. Helmericks:]Martha, Bud, Mark and Jeffrey Helmericks and our cessua 310 in Fairbanks Alaska. 1974. The fog are Lhasa apsos from Tibet, 1
    - Verso: Martha, Bud, Mark and Jeffrey Helmericks and our cessua 310 in Fairbanks Alaska. 1974. The fog are Lhasa apsos from Tibet, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Harmon R. Helmericks], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Harmon R. Helmericks], 3